That little one looks tender.
Must be delicious.
Go report to the Chief.
Tell him lunch is sorted for today.
Delicious?
Lunch?
How can they eat people?
They are demons,
and they cultivate the physical body.
Eating humans is cultivation
to them.
I already know.
But these people look extraordinary.
They are not something you can just eat.
You trespassed into
my Black Wind Stronghold.
What is your business here?
You must be Hei Wuya.
Hand over the Black Holy Crystal,
and we will spare your lives.
Hahaha.
You want the Black Holy Crystal?
Let's see if you have what it takes.
A'kong,
do I have to make a move again?
You sent such a little thing?
Brothers, attack!
No.
Just a little more.
She needs pressure.
My Lady is using...
my moves.
And such strong spiritual power.
She copied Feng's moves.
If it is the power of Nuwa,
there should be a distance limit
from the one being copied.
As long as Feng is far enough away,
her copying will fail.
Feng,
go take out those archers outside.
Yes, sir.
What is going on?
My spiritual power...
Ah!
Never mind, saving my life
is more important.
Chief, those archers
have been taken care of.
M-My Lady...
If the power of Nuwa inside her
cannot be awakened on its own,
it will become her death warrant.
Only a desperate situation
can awaken her.
Otherwise, she will forever
be just a shell
controlled by power.
Stand up, A'kong.
He doesn't believe me,
so he wants these people to kill me.
Why?
Why can he
control my life and death at will?
You want to see me die,
but I refuse to.
My life is my own.
W-What is that?
Survive.
How is this possible?
She didn't die from such injuries.
Is she even human?
Are you satisfied, sir?
If you wanted to kill me,
why go to such lengths?
Chief,
My Lady...
Hand over the Black Holy Crystal.
H-Here you go.
Chief,
is this stone really
more important than My Lady?
This is my mother's relic.
It went missing after she died.
I only found its whereabouts
a century ago.
But My Lady...
We walk different paths
from her after all.
Let's continue our journey
to Qiong City.
Send someone to follow her.
In secret.
Do not let her notice.
Where am I?
The dungeon.
It's been two days.
You were heavily injured
and haven't had a drop of water,
yet you are still alive.
Oh no.
It's the survivor from that day.
Hmph. It seems you still remember me.
I wanted to kill you right away,
but it's a pity
the Left Protector wants to see you.
Come with me.
Great job, Chilian.
I need to find a way to escape first.
What are you muttering to yourself?
I told you to get up and come with me.
Didn't you hear me?
I heard you.
I am going.
No one treated me.
How did my wounds heal?
Oh no, it's a dead end.
Your physical strength
is truly surprising.
Oh no.
Down there is...